《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously, on "The Flash"...
我可以做一些很酷的事情  你知道吗
I can do some cool things, you know?
有时候我跑得很快  能够扭转一点点时间
Sometimes I run so fast, I reverse time a bit.
免费的黑暗风暴
Dark and Stormy on the house.
我看起来很可怜吗
Do I look that pathetic?
你看起来和我一样属于这里
You look like you belong here about as much as I do.
-西斯科  -卡米拉
- Cisco. - Kamilla.
我们可能找到了抑制超能力者基因组的办法
We may have found a way to suppress the meta genome.
好极了  这样我们就可以让蝉失去超能力
Great, then we can use it to de-power Cicada,
-一劳永逸  -你又是谁
- stop him for good. - Who the hell are you?
我是一名记者
I'm a reporter.
我们会打败你的
We're gonna beat you.
你挺厉害啊
Damn, you're good.
真的厉害
Real good.
好像太厉害了
Maybe too good.
解药合成100%
我们成功了
We did it.
We did it!
天哪
Oh, my.
西斯科·雷蒙  你今晚搞到了
Cisco Ramon, tonight you've got yourself
热辣的约会和治愈超能力者的解药
a hot date and a meta-human cure.
我们已无可阻挡
We're unstoppable.
完蛋...
Ooh, shrap...
闪 电 侠
第五季
第十四集
我们还要等多久
We have to wait how long
才能使用治愈超能力者的解药
before we can use the meta-human cure?
不用多久
Not even that long.
-西斯科  -也就打个响指的时间
- Cisco. - It's gonna go by like that.
西斯科
Cisco.
-二十九天  -一个月
- 29 days. - A month?
没错吧  只要短短一个月而已
I know, right? Just one, teeny, tiny, month
我们就能阻止蝉的大屠杀了
until we stop Cicada's purge. You know,
从历史的角度来看  这比我们之前
historically speaking, this is way faster
打败大反派的速度快多了...
than we've ever stopped a big bad so...
我们等不了那么久
We can't wait that long.
如果他发现新的超能力者
If he finds another meta
或者来袭击我们...  我们必须加快速度
or comes after us--we have to speed this up somehow.
必须等化合物充分合成
We have to wait for the compound to fully synthesize
否则它无法有效地中和
or it won't be able to effectively neutralize
超能力者脑下垂体里的暗物质
the dark matter in a meta-human's pituitary gland.
如果不能加快变异演化...
Without any way to expedite the exotic evolution--
巴里  我们必须等
Barry, we're gonna have to wait.
我们只能等了
I think we have to wait.
除非...
Unless...
你把它带进神速力
you took it into the Speed Force.
怎么  你想让他
What, you want him to go into
去神速力里呆一个月  然后怎样
the Speed Force for a month and then, what,
出来回到他离开的那天吗
come out the same day that he left?
不不不  我没说让你操纵时间
Oh, no, no, I'm not saying you manipulate time.
我是说让你操纵暗物质
I'm saying you manipulate dark matter.
这很简单  基础化学  对吧
So very simple. It's simple chemistry, right?
你合成化合物的时候要用...
When you are synthesizing a compound, you use a--
反应物  基质...
commodity, uh, substrate, uh--
-催化剂  -对  催化剂
- A catalyst? - Catalyst, right.
而合成能够抵消暗物质的化合物时
And the most efficient catalyst you can use when synthesizing
最高效的催化剂
a compound that negates dark matter
就是超光速的粒子
is superluminal particles.
-快子  -很好
- Tachyons? - Très bien.
就是快子  快子最密集的地方在哪里
Tachyons, and the place where tachyons are the most dense?
-神速力  -就是这样
- Speed Force. - And voilà.
或许行得通
That might actually work.
的确行得通  这就好比
Yeah, it will. It'll be like nuking it
把它放到全维度微波炉里加热
in a pan-dimensional microwave.
-主意不错  -我知道
-Nice work. - I know.
那这样能节约多少时间
So how much time would this save?
从二十九天缩短到六十分钟
From 29 days down to 60 minutes.
这样就快多了
Yeah, it's gonna be faster.
而且从你们上次交手后
And also since Cicada has been quiet
蝉一直没什么动静
since your last encounter,
现在应该是最佳时机了
maybe there's no time like the present.
-去吧  -好
- Do it. - All right.
一小时后见
I'll see you in an hour.
诺拉  你得留在这里
Nora, you need to stay here.
你不要我帮忙吗
You don't want my help?
我只是...  这次我来搞定
I just-- I got this one this time.
你确定现在去合适吗
Are you sure that now is a good time to go?
我只是说  这座城市会少了闪电侠
I mean, I just mean, the city will be Flash-less,
缺少闪电侠的一小时是很久的
and an hour is a long time to be without the Flash.
这座城市不会少了闪电侠的  还有XS呢
The city is not gonna be Flash-less. It'll have XS.
但是那次
Yeah, but what about the time
你被迫在管道监狱牢房里待了一天
you had to spend 24 hours in the Pipeline cell
天气女巫和银色幽灵就偷了天眼会的车
and Weather Witch and Silver Ghost stole that A.R.G.U.S. car--
虽然我不在  但是你阻止了他们
And you stopped them without me.
蝉差点对老妈下手的事
Eh, with what happened to Mom because of Cicada--
爱瑞丝没事的  这是阻止蝉的关键部分
Iris is fine, and this is the key to stopping Cicada.
我要走了
I gotta go.
如果有事发生  照我教你的去做
If anything happens, just do what I've trained you to do:
放慢速度  先想清楚
slow down and think clearly.
-好  -我相信你  你要相信你自己
- Yeah. - I trust you, you just gotta trust yourself.
你可以的
You'll be fine.
就一个小时
60 minutes.
诺拉  西斯科还没去约会吧
Nora, Cisco hasn't left for his date yet, has he?
应该没有
Uh, I don't think so.
那好  我们还有一次机会
Great, we get another chance at this.
是的  所以你不会这么做
Well, it is-- that's why you don't do it.
-怎么了  -没事
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
天呐  不要再拿《拉尔夫之书》来说事了
Oh, God. Not the "Book of Ralph" again!
《拉尔夫之书》
兄弟  你成功地完成了
Yeah, buddy. You successfully completed
我那忘记你挚爱的27个步骤
my 27 steps to getting over the love of your life.
吉普赛已经是过去式了
Gypsy is in the past.
现在你有了新欢
You have a new siren,
所以是时候看
so now it's time for...
《爱情艺术》
"The Art of Love."
凯特琳
Um, Caitlin?
我要完成注射解药的装置
I've gotta finish working on the device to inject the cure.
我也得把解药注射进装置里
Also I have to inject the device for the cure.
爱...  爱瑞丝
I-- I-- I-- Iris?
不  你自己搞定吧
Oh, no, this is all you, man.
我有文章要写
I got an article I gotta write.
巴里回来了通知我
Let me know when Barry gets back.
救救我
Help me.
《第一章  初步计划》
"Chapter one: Initial Planning."
初步计划
Initial planning?
这是第一次约会  孙子  不是去打仗
It's a first date, Sun Tzu, not an incursion.
相信我  蚱蜢
Trust me, Grasshopper,
爱情如战场  但是也行
love is war, but, fine,
如果你想直接跳到《第六章  掌握地形》
if you wanna skip to chapter six, "Know Your Terrain."
-我们约在吉特  -熟悉的地形
- We're meeting at Jitters. - Ah, familiar territory.
你学到了
You are learning.
他真该走了
Uh, you know, he really should be going.
-是的  -等等  等一下
- I really should. - Hang on, hang on one second.
这个真的很重要
This one's really important.
《第十三章  情报与侦察》
Chapter thirteen, "Intelligence and Reconnaissance."
你在网上调查卡米拉
Wh-- you cyber-stalked Kamilla?
不不不  当然没有
No, no, no, no, of course not.
这是她公开的个人信息
That's her public profile.
但是正好有些信息
But it did happen to have some info
是关于她可能会喜欢的男人类型
on the types of guys that she might be into.
她喜欢的男人类型
The types of guys that she's into?
没错  可惜你完全不符合要求
Yes, and, unfortunately, you are nothing like them,
但如果你不想和她约会第二次  随你便
but, hey, if you don't wanna get a second date, be my guest.
只是别在事情搞砸
Just don't come crying to me when everything inevitably
你要孤独终老的时候  来找我哭诉
goes horribly, horribly wrong and you die alone.
没什么大不了的
No big deal.
这下他的话在脑里挥之不去了
See, now he's in my head.
不用  谢了
Okay, no thank you.
我没拿这些
I didn't take these.
-你什么也没看到  -没看到
- You saw nothing. - Nothing.
伊恩的蝉咖啡
One Cicada on the bar for Ian?
-是艾恩  -抱歉  艾恩
- It's I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
卡米拉
Hey, Kamilla.
西斯科
Cisco. Wow.
抱歉我迟到了  会议结束晚了
Sorry I'm late. I got held up at a meeting.
没事  我也刚到
That's okay. I just got here.
早知道这样  我就穿好点衣服来了
If I'd had known, I would have dressed up more.
这件老古董啊
Oh, this old thing?
不是的  这是工作服
No, please, this is work clothes.
你实验室需要穿西服吗
You have to wear a suit to your lab?
我的实验室
My lab?
我们在酒吧认识的时候
When we met at the bar,
你在谈DNA和基因组
you were talking about DNA and genomes,
所以我以为你是科学家之类的
so I assumed you were some kind of scientist.
是  我是说了  科学家
Right, I said that, scientist.
是  不是  我是那种你们叫做
Yes. No. Well, I'm what you would call
科学企业家的人
a science businessman.
所以呢  你是用别人的发明赚钱吗
So, what, you make money off of other people's discoveries?
总得有人去做不是
Well, somebody has to.
就是个小玩笑  我经常说这种话
It's just a little joke, something I always say.
那你公司的名字叫什么
So, uh, what is the name of the company you work for?
叫做拉蒙工业
It's called Ramon Industries.
你用自己名字起的吗
It's named after yourself?
真谦逊
That's humble.
也许我该去给咱俩买杯咖啡
Maybe I should grab us a couple coffees.
好吧
Sure.
-脱因闪电侠  -脱因闪电侠  好的
- Decaf Flash. - Decaf Flash, right, okay.
不只有你一个人会做调查
You're not the only one who does their research.
我知道你是谁  爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦
I know who you are, Iris West-Allen.
我知道你和闪电侠还有其他英雄合作
I know you work with the Flash and the other heroes.
你说你们会打败我
You said you were gonna beat me,
但今晚  我将会打败你
but tonight, I'm gonna beat you,
你们所有人
all of you.
一杯极速和一杯脱因闪电侠
One Zoom and one decaf Flash.
这是脱因的  这城市里的男人
That's the decaf. Men in this city...
还用说吗
Tell me about it.
真对不起  是工作  我得走了
Uh, I'm sorry, it's work. I have to go.
求救广播
我们能不能重新约一次  求你了
Uh, could we just have, like, a do-over, please?
警报广播 爱瑞丝位置
是妈妈
It's Mom.
离开她身边
Get away from her.
你想要的不是她
She's not who you want.
对  她不是  但你们是
No, she's not, but you are.
那就来抓我们吧
Then come and get us.
凯特琳
Caitlin!
告诉过你了
Told ya.
诺拉  西斯科还没去约会吧
Nora, Cisco hasn't left for his date yet, has he?
应该没有
Uh, I don't think so.
那好  我们还有一次机会
Great, I get another chance at this.
确实还有一次机会
We do.
-怎么了  -没什么
- What's wrong? - Uh, nothing.
就是得解决这问题  好吧
I just have to fix this. Okay.
天呐  不要再拿
Oh, God, not the...
《拉尔夫之书》
"Book of Ralph."
-来说事了  -兄弟
- Again! - Yeah, buddy,
你成功地完成了
You have successfully completed my 27 steps
我那忘记你挚爱的27个步骤
to getting over the love of your life.
吉普赛已经是过去式了  现在你有了新欢
Gypsy is in the past, you have a new siren,
所以是时候看《爱情艺术》了
so now it's time for the Art of Love.
凯特琳
Um, Caitlin?
我要完成注射解药的装置
I gotta go finish the device to inject the cure.
我也得把解药注射进装置里
Also have to inject the device for the cure.
-爱瑞丝  -不  你自己搞定吧
- I--I--I--Iris? - Oh, no, this is all you, man.
我有篇文章要去写
I got an article I gotta write.
巴里回来了通知我
Let me know when Barry gets back.
真不酷炫
So not shway.
《第一章  初步计划》
"Chapter one: Initial Planning."
-你不能走  -什么
- Uh, you can't leave. - What?
我是说  你不能去你的办公室
I mean, you just shouldn't go to your office,
-现在不行  -为什么
- not right now. - Why?
因为爸爸会回来  马上就会
Because Dad is gonna be back, like, any minute
然后当你到那里的时候
and by the time that you get there,
就只能再原路返回
you're just gonna have to turn around anyway.
我知道  但我今晚就得完成这文章
Yeah, I know, but I need to get this article out tonight.
是  但是你带着笔记本电脑呢  对吗
Yeah, but, I mean, you have your laptop with you, right?
为什么不在这里写
So why don't you just write it here
在安全的休息室里写
in the lounge where it's safe?
安全
Safe?
我是说舒适  这里很舒适
I mean cozy. It's cozy.
好吧  这样也行
Um, yeah, I mean, yeah. I guess I could.
太好了  我去给你做咖啡
Great, I'll make you coffee.
-好的  -太好了
- Ok. -OK
你最后会孤独地死去
You end up dying alone.
这下他的话在脑里挥之不去了
Okay, see, now he's in my head.
不了谢谢  拉尔夫
No thank you, Ralph.
该死
Dang it.
那是最后一瓶了
Last bottle.
拉尔夫·德比
私家侦探
伊恩的一杯蝉咖啡
One Cicada at the bar for Ian.
-是艾恩  -抱歉  艾恩
- It's I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
-卡米拉  你好  -西斯科
- Kamilla, hey. - Cisco, wow.
抱歉来晚了  我刚从健身房过来
Sorry I'm late. I just came from the gym.
你得运动到足够的步数  对吧
Ya gotta get your steps in, you know?
没关系  我刚到
That's okay, I just got here.
你经常健身吗
You work out a lot?
当然了  我就是个健身狂热者
You kidding me? I'm, like, a gym rat, you know.
我成天都在健身房里
I live there.
你常做的健身项目是什么
So what kind of workouts do you do?
我没什么不做的项目  我会做
What kind of workouts don't I do? I mean, like,
加强核心肌肉的普拉提
Pilates for the core,
锻炼股四头肌的增强式训练
plyometrics for the quads,
循环训练  基本上所有
circuit training, I mean, pretty much anything
我能接触到的项目  甚至是我的手
I can get my hands on, even my hands, you know.
大家都知道我会
I've been known to do some
时不时地做手指俯卧撑
you know, finger pushups every once in a while.
-怎么了  -我们在酒吧遇到的时候
- What? - When we met at the bar,
你在谈论DNA和基因组
you were talking about DNA and genomes, so--
所以你以为我不是你喜欢的类型
So you thought maybe I wasn't your type?
我以为我终于遇到了一个
I thought I had finally met a guy who was more concerned
认为头脑发达比四肢发达更重要的人了
with flexing his brain than his muscles.
好吧  我去给我俩买两杯咖啡
Okay, um, maybe I should grab us a couple of coffees.
好的  我要一杯脱因闪电侠
Sure, decaf Flash.
脱因闪电侠  我正要问你
Decaf Flash, I was gonna ask you.
我知道你是谁  伸缩人
I know who you are, Elongated Man.
我知道你和闪电侠还有其他英雄一起工作
I know you work with the Flash and the other heroes.
爱瑞丝·韦斯特·艾伦说你们会打败我
Iris West-Allen told me you were gonna beat me.
但是今晚
But tonight,
我会打败你们
I'm gonna beat you,
你们所有人
all of you.
-一杯极速  一杯脱因闪电侠  -谢谢
- One Zoom and one decaf Flash. - Thanks.
-这座城市里的男人  -可不是吗
- The men in this city. - Tell me about it.
这杯是脱咖啡因的  这座城市里的男人
That's the decaf. The men in this city...
可不是吗
Tell me about it.
抱歉  健身房有紧急情况
Uh, I'm sorry, it's a gym emergency.
我得走了  我们可以重新再约一次吗
I have to go. Um, can we just have a do-over, please?
警报广播 拉尔夫位置
-拉尔夫  -去找凯特琳
- Ralph. - Get Caitlin.
好
Okay.
快躲开
Move!
拉尔夫
Ralph?
告诉过你了
Told ya.
诺拉  西斯科还没去约会吧
Nora, Cisco hasn't left for his date yet, has he?
没有  我确定他还没去
Uh, no, I'm pretty sure he hasn't.
那好  我们还有一次机会
Great, I'm gonna get another chance at this.
没错  我们还有机会
Yeah, we do.
怎么了
What's wrong?
诺拉
Nora?
没事  加油  你能找到办法
Nothing. Come on, you can figure this out.
不要再拿《拉尔夫之书》来说事了
Not the "Book of Ralph" Again!
兄弟  你成功地完成了
Yeah, buddy, you successfully completed my 27 steps
我那忘记你挚爱的27个步骤
to getting over the love of your life.
吉普赛已经是过去式了  现在你有了新欢
Gypsy is in the past. You have a new siren,
现在是时候用《爱情艺术》了
so now it's time for "The Art of Love."
凯特琳
Um, Caitlin?
我要完成注射解药的装置
I gotta go work on the device to inject the cure.
我得去研究解药
Also I have to devise the cure.
爱瑞丝
I--I--I--Iris?
不  你自己搞定吧
Ooh, nah, that's all you, man.
我得去写文章
I gotta go write an article.
巴里回来了通知我
Let me know when Barry gets back.
别  不要去
Uh, no, you know what? Don't go.
你什么不在这里写文章
Uh, why don't you write the article here?
我可以给你做咖啡
Uh, I can make you coffee.
我是说  我知道那里也有咖啡
I mean, I know that there's coffee over there, but I--
我只是觉得在老爸回来之前
I just think it's really important for the team leader
队长留在这里非常重要
to stay here until Dad gets back
以防不测  好吗
just in case something happens, okay?
好吧  那我去休息室
Okay, lounge it is.
好了  《第一章  初步计划》
All right, "Chapter one: Initial Planning."
这是第一次约会  孙子  又不是打仗
It's a first date, Sun Tzu, not an incursion.
相信我  蚱蜢  爱情就是场战争
Trust me, Grasshopper, love is war.
是啊  我非常同意  所以看看这个
Yeah, and I couldn't agree more, so read these.
会对你有帮助  然后你会知道该怎么做
They'll help you, and you'll know what to do.
-等等  怎么  -如果出岔子了
- Wait, wait, how-- - And if anything goes wrong,
打电话给我们
just give us a call.
你和我留在这  喝我们自己的咖啡
You and I are gonna stay here and have our own coffees
-就在休息室里  -不  不
- in the lounge. - No, no, no.
有巧克力蛋糕哦
There's brownies.
-有巧克力蛋糕吗  -是的
- Brownies? - Yes.
拉尔夫  你是不是在网上调查她了
Ralph, did you cyber-stalk her?
你当时在谈论DNA和基因组
You were talking about DNA and genomes.
我以为我终于遇见一个
I thought I'd finally met a guy who was more concerned
更在意自己的大脑而不是肌肉的人
with flexing his brain than his muscles.
还好吗
Ca va?
我没事  没事  抱歉  我只是
Yeah, yeah. Sorry, I just--
我刚刚产生了特别离奇的似曾相识感
I'm having the most wicked déjà vu right now.
是吗
Is that right?
你为什么不想你母亲来这呢
Why don't you want your mother to come here, hmm?
因为你时间旅行来过了
Because you time-travel.
-我叫艾恩  -抱歉  艾恩
- It's I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
令人激动的卡米拉
Kamilla tha thrilla.
西斯科
Cisco?
-天呐  -抱歉我迟到了
- Wow. - Sorry I'm late.
我刚从一个拍摄赶过来
I just came from a photoshoot.
为了照片墙美照不惜一切  对吧
The things you do for the 'gram, am I right?
也许下次你应该做我的摄影师
Hey, maybe next time you should be my photographer.
你觉得如何
What do you think?
所以你是一个
So you're a...
我正励志成为一名网红
I'm an aspiring social media influencer.
这是我的名片  你可以留着
This is my card. You can keep that.
我们在酒吧认识的时候
When we met at the bar,
你在谈论DNA和基因组
you were talking about DNA and genomes,
所以我以为你是科学家之类的
so I assumed you were some kind of scientist.
真的吗  我们在酒吧认识的时候
Really? When we met at the bar,
你在谈论DNA和基因组  所以...
you were talking about DNA and genomes, so I--
所以我以为你是科学家之类的
You assumed I was some kind of scientist?
是啊  没错
Yeah, exactly.
你还好吗
Is everything okay?
我没事  我只是又产生似曾相识感了
Yeah, I'm just having some déjà vu again.
也许我该去给咱俩买杯咖啡
Maybe I should grab us a couple of coffees?
好的  那太好了
Oh, yes. Yes, that'd be great.
请你给我点杯极速  好吗
Will you get me a Zoom, please?
好的
Okay.
怎么回事
What?
好了  请用
Okay, here we go.
谢谢
Thanks.
-一杯极速和一杯脱因闪电侠  -谢谢
- One Zoom and one decaf Flash. - Thank you.
不太对劲
Something's wrong,
-我想我得走了  -现在吗
- and I think I have to go. - Right now?
不  现在
No, right now.
求救广播
没错  我得走了  我本想问问
Yep, gotta go. Um, I'd ask if we could have
我们能不能再约一次
a do-over, but, um,
不过我感觉已经约过了
something tells me I already have.
-这城市里的男人  -还用说吗
- The men in this city. - Tell me about it.
警报广播 歇洛克位置
-不是吧  -歇洛克出事了
- Come on! - It's Sherloque.
什么  我以为他和凯特琳在这里
What? I thought he was here with Caitlin.
-我们得去找冰霜杀手  -不  我来搞定
- We gotta get Frost. - No, no, I got this.
你们待在这
You guys just stay here.
孩子  小心
Garçon, look out!
告诉过你了
Told ya.
西斯科
Cisco!
我为什么解决不了这事
Why can't I fix this?
我为什么不能回到更早的时间了
Why can't I go back any further?
-诺拉  -西斯科还没走
- Nora? - Cisco hasn't left yet.
太好了
Great.
所以我们还有一次机会
So we get another chance at this.
是的
We do.
我没事  歇洛克
I'm fine, Sherloque.
我要解决这事
I have to fix this.
[法语]
好吧  你们必须待在这里
Okay, you guys have to stay here.
为什么
Why?
因为我爸完全信任我能保护你们所有人
Because dad put his trust in me that I would protect all of you
这是我第一次当这里唯一的极速者
and I'm the only speedster here for the first time
如果出了什么问题
and if something were to go wrong,
我不知道我能不能解决
I don't know if I could fix it, in fact,
我很确定我解决不了  所以就待在这一小时
I'm pretty sure that I couldn't fix it, so just, for one hour, stay here.
我得去搞定...
I have to go finish--
不  不
No, no!
我有个约会...
I got a date with--
你在人肉卡米拉吗
Were you cyber-stalking Kamilla?
不不不  当然没有
No, no, no, of course not.
这是她的公开资料
This is her public profile.
你在谈DNA和基因组
You were talking about DNA and genomes,
所以我以为我终于认识了一个
so I thought I'd finally met a guy
更在意自己的大脑而不是肌肉的人
who is more concerned with his brain than his muscles.
卡米拉
Kamilla.
关于她喜欢哪种男人  我掌握了一些细节
Oh, I got some details on the kinds of guys she's into.
等等  你在网上调查她吗
Wait, were you cyber-stalking her?
不  我没调查她  那是她的公开资料
No, I'm not stalking her. It's her public profile.
各位  我很抱歉  但你们得待在这里
Guys! I'm sorry, but you're just gonna have to stay here.
-艾恩 -对不起  艾恩
- I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
对不起 卡米拉
我得忙工作
今晚没法陪你
你在跟我开玩笑吧
You have got to be kidding me.
你拿到了第一个
You got the first one.
-我拿到了第二个  -我觉得我们都有一个
- I got the next one. - I think we all got one.
你拿到了什么
What did you get?
警报广播 塞西尔位置
-是塞西尔  -各位  待在这里
- It's Cecile. - Guys, um, just stay here.
跟你说过了
Told ya.
诺拉
Nora?
我本应该保护你们
I was supposed to protect you,
但我办不到  我不知道该怎么做
but I can't. I don't know how to.
但我爸知道
But my dad does.
我也不能进入神速力了吗
I can't get into the Speed Force either?
你在逆转时间  是吗
You're reversing time, aren't you?
我解决不了
And I can't fix it.
所以我们都会死吗
So all of us die?
有些时候是  或是你们中的某个人
Sometimes, or just one of you.
有时候是塞西尔  但每次都至少有一个人
Sometimes Cecile, but every time, there's at least one.
我就说有种似曾相识的感觉
I thought I was having déjà vu.
我一遍又一遍看到我和卡米拉的约会
I keep seeing my date with Kamilla again and again,
我照着这指南走每次下场都很惨
me failing miserably every time by using these.
这不是似曾相识
I'm not having déjà vu.
是我在一遍又一遍震波过去的时间
I'm vibing the past hour over and over.
是的
Yeah.
这发生多少次了
How many times has this happened?
-五十二次  -五十二次
- 52. - 52?
这是传奇们推断的固定点理论之一是吗
This is one of those fixed points the Legends theorized, isn't it?
没有办法阻止我们中的一个人去死
There's no way to keep one of us from dying.
-我们得把巴里找来  -不  我试过了
- We have to get Barry. - No, I tried that,
但是我身上出了问题
but there's something wrong with me.
我进不了神速力
I can't get into the Speed Force.
那我们只能在这里等到他回来
Well, then we'll just wait here until he gets back.
不  如果我们这么做  蝉会杀了塞西尔
No, if we do that, Cicada will kill Cecile.
所以把时间倒转到他走之前
So just reverse time and go back to before he left.
不  我也试过了  但我控制不了
No, I've tried that too, but I can't control it.
我做什么都不重要  什么都不管用
It doesn't matter what I try to do. Nothing works!
信不信由你  这并不是我第一次
Believe it or not, this ain't the first time
死在过去的时间线上
I've died in a past timeline.
有一次我的胸口被一只震动的手穿过
I once got a vibrating hand through the chest
拜艾尔伯德·斯旺所赐
courtesy of Eobard Thawne.
经历过不止一次
Well, more than once.
我不断地去回顾那个时刻  直到我发现
I actually kept vibing that moment until I realized
那实际上发生过
that it actually happened.
事到如今我也没什么好惊讶的才对
I guess I should have known the same thing was happening now, huh?
我已竭尽所能改变未来
I keep trying my absolute hardest to change the outcome,
但每次都以失败告终
but I end up failing every time.
如果结局无法改变怎么办  西斯科
What if we can't fix this, Cisco?
诺拉  有时候我们会失败
Nora, sometimes we fail because
是因为我们太害怕失败了
all we worry about is not failing.
和辛西娅分手后我总担心自己的初次约会
I'm so worried about my first date since Cynthia
不敢在卡米拉面前暴露本心
that I don't feel free to be myself around Kamilla,
最后反而弄巧成拙
and then I'll just end up screwing it up even more.
就算再聪明再会洞察人心
This--this intelligence and reconnaissance mess,
都不是我想要的  我只想做我自己
I don't need this. All I need is to be myself.
我更不想打扮成奥佐恩的样子
And I sure as hell don't need to dress up like Ozone
只为讨好卡米拉
just to impress Kamilla.
抱歉  这个梗对你来说过时了
Sorry, that is an outdated reference.
不过时  是电影《霹雳舞》中的角色
No, from the movie "Breakin'."
我也看过《霹雳舞2》
Yeah, I've seen "Electric Boogaloo" Too.
这两个我都看过上百回了
I've seen them both, like, a hundred times.
我很熟悉他们的每一个舞步
I know every move.
脑残粉
Wow, fangirl.
等等
Wait.
等会  对了
Wait, that's it.
我每次失败都会在日记里记笔记
Every time I fail, I take notes in my journal
这样下次就不会重蹈覆辙
so I can do something different the next time.
一举一动都尽在掌握中
We know every move.
你只需要告诉我们
So all you need to do is just tell us
你做过的一切尝试以及最后怎么失败的
everything you've done and how it went wrong.
这样就能想办法扭转乾坤了
So we can figure out how to make it right.
52起绑架案就是52种排列组合
52 kidnappings, 52 combinations
引向着52种死亡
leading to 52 deaths.
-但这些不包含蝉的  -没错
- None of them were Cicada's? - Exactly.
对  没错
Yes, exactly.
你想借着诺拉逆转时间的机会
Wait, does that mean you want to use Cicada's dagger against him
利用蝉的匕首来对付他
by having Nora reverse time?
我就是这个意思
That's exactly what I'm suggesting.
我们要怎么做呢
Yeah, but how are we gonna do that?
诺拉逆转时间的时候会失去控制
I mean, Nora can't control it when she reverses time.
我们帮她放慢逆转速度就能让她控制自己
She could control her abilities if we help her slow down.
蝉抛出匕首
放慢逆转速度
Slowing it down.
如果真能做到这点  就能主动出击
If she can do that, we bring the fight to him.
我们就都能撑过这一晚
And we all live through the night.
我喜欢这个计划
I like the sound of that.
一切都已准备就绪
Well, we have everything we need.
在找我吗  我知道你调查了我
Looking for me? I know you did your research.
你知道我是谁  我是闪电侠
You know who I am, that I work for the Flash
以及其他英雄们的队友
and the other heroes.
我说过我们一定能打败你
I told you we were gonna beat you,
而今晚就是决胜之夜
and tonight we will...
我们所有人
All of us.
快点  就现在
Allez, now!
警告过你了
Told you.
未发现暗物质痕迹
未发现暗物质  德怀尔又消失了
No dark matter anywhere. Dwyer's gone, again.
他刚被教训了一番
Maybe after the ass kicking he just got,
再想找我们麻烦可得三思了
he'll think twice before coming after us again.
他要是不三思一下  你就给他点颜色看看
And if he doesn't think twice, now you can make him.
谢谢你帮助我放慢逆转速度
Thanks for helping me slow it down.
既然体验到控制能力的感觉
Now that I've experienced a sense of control,
也许下次不用帮忙我也能控制自己了
maybe next time, I can do it on my own.
谢谢你救了我们  我们所有人
Thank you for saving us, all of us.
有些事不是我能解决的
I didn't save everything.
需要你去争取
Maybe you can now?
不了  不了  约会早就结束了
No, no, that date is over.
卡米拉肯定不在吉特咖啡馆
There's no way Kamilla's still at Jitters.
她要是还在的话
Well, if she is still there,
也许这里的东西
there might be some stuff
拉尔夫之书
能让你缓和下尴尬的局面
in here that can help you smooth things over.
但你可以处理好的  你可是西斯科·拉蒙
But, you can handle it. You're Cisco Ramon.
去吧  你该走了
Come on, you gotta get a move on.
好吧
Okay.
-跑啊  罗密欧  -我在动了
- Giddyap, Romeo. - I'm moving.
好的
Okay.
歇洛克是对的  一小时就好了
Sherloque was right. One hour, it's cooked.
我不在的时候发生了什么吗
Something happen while I was gone?
史蒂文的"闪电小子"好了
Kid Flash on the bar for Steven?
-是史蒂芬  -抱歉  史蒂芬
- It's Stephan. - Sorry, Stephan.
-嘿  卡米拉  -西斯科
- Kamilla, hey. - Cisco
对不起我迟到了  我在工作上遇到了紧急情况
I am so sorry I'm late. I had an emergency at work.
没关系  我刚到
It's okay, I just got here.
你是个科学家  是吗
So you're a scientist, right?
我们在酒吧的时候
When we were at the bar,
你在谈论DNA和基因组  所以
you were talking about DNA and genomes, so...
事实上  我是个科技宅
I'm more of a tech nerd, actually,
但我们正在进行的项目
but the project that we're working on now,
开始变得非常科学
it gets very scientific.
你听起来对此非常地兴奋
You sound like you're really excited about it.
没错  我非常地兴奋
Oh, my God, I am. I'm so excited about it.
你绝对无法想象
You have no idea, um.
我想我们最近可能取得了突破
I think we might have made a breakthrough recently,
一项足以改变众人人生的突破
a breakthrough that could change a lot of lives.
一杯极速与一杯脱因闪电侠
One Zoom and one decaf Flash.
我希望你不介意  我预先打电话叫了
I hope you don't mind, I called it in ahead of time.
这是至少我能做的
It's the least I could do.
-那杯是脱因的  -你怎么知道我喜欢这种
- That's the decaf. - How did you know what I like?
我有种感觉
I had a feeling.
不像这个城市里的其他男人
Not like most of the men in this city.
还用你说
Tell me about it.
听着  我知道像这样迟到
Listen, I know I screwed up royally
真的搞砸了
showing up late like this,
但我会非常地开心  如果
but it would make me very happy if--
我们可以重新来一遍  拜托
Can we just have a do-over, please?
听起来不错
That sounds nice.
五十二次
52 times?
五十三次  如果你包括这次的话
53, if you include now.
那很多遍了
That's a lot.
我该怎么做  就让他们其中一个死去吗
What was I supposed to do, let one of them die?
问题是  诺拉  时间旅行是有后果的
The thing is, Nora, there are consequences to time travel.
-我知道  -不  你不懂
- Oh, I know. - No, you don't,
不像我一样了解
not like I do.
让我来告诉你
Let me show you something.
想像这个咖啡杯是时空连续体
Imagine this coffee cup is the space/time continuum.
每次你回到过去  它都会破裂
Whenever you go back in time, it breaks.
你可以试着重设时间线
Now, you can try and reset the timeline,
或者试着修补它  但不管你怎么尝试
try and fix it, but no matter how hard you try,
它永远不会和原来的一模一样
it's never gonna be exactly how it was.
这次看起来成功了
It seems like things worked out this time,
但不会永远是这样  而我们也不可能
but that's not always gonna be true,
知道这些改变将会如何呈现
and it's impossible to know how these changes are gonna unfold,
或是你制造的涟漪  还有你会改变哪些人的人生
the ripples you'll cause, whose life you're gonna affect.
没有人能做到
No one can do that.
没有人
No one?
没有
No one.
我们不是神  诺拉
We're not gods, Nora.
我们只是被赋予了超凡的能力
We've just been given extraordinary abilities.
符号数据库已更新 是否翻译剩余符号
斯旺  我要知道我们不会把这变得更糟
Thawne, I need to know we're not making this worse.
告诉我你知道你在做什么
Tell me you know what you're doing.
我是唯一知道自己在做什么的极速者
I am the only speedster who knows what he's doing!
按照计划进行
Stick with the plan.
依循我的指示我们就能打败蝉
Follow my instructions and we'll defeat Cicada,
我们就能摧毁他的匕首
we'll destroy his dagger,
然后我们就可以救你的父亲
and then we will save your father.